(Howard:)You saw what's under this robe,
and you still married me.
(Bernadette:)If you're really worried,
we'll take him to the vet
(Bernadette:)and have him tested.
Good.
(Howard:)Thank you. Oh, okay,
there is a test!
(Howard:)All they have to do is...
(Howard:)cut off his head
and check his brain.
(Bernadette:)Oh, cut off his head?
(Bernadette:)That's where
his little nose is.
(Howard:)He's not showing
any symptoms.
(Howard:)I guess I'll just go to the
emergency room to be safe.
(Bernadette:)Howie, this is just
your hypochondria.
(Howard:)No, when I sat
on the mute button
(Howard:)and thought I'd gone deaf,
that was my hypochondria.
(Bernadette:)We'll find another time
to tell him I'm pregnant.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
I mean, this is the first time
(Raj(voice):)I've ever broken up
with someone.
(Raj(voice):)I just... I didn't realize
it was gonna hurt this much.